top-password.com 2011-06-02

# Privacy policy

|  | 

## Your Information Remains Private  
  
---  
Our policy is that we do not share customer information with anyone. We do not give it away, and we do not sell this information to any third party. If you entrust us with your information, we keep it from anyone else. Customer data is not made public for any reason. We use it only to communicate with customers. We do not use your information for any purpose outside the scope of communicating with you in the most efficient manner.  
---  
  
## Virus-free files guaranteed  
  
All of the files posted on our web site are scanned for any potential virus before they are uploaded. We guarantee that the programs you download from us will not be infected in any way.  
---  
  
## Clean software  
  
Our software does not contain any adware, spyware or other invading processes to extract information from your system or otherwise annoy you with information.   
---  
  
## Purchasing  
  
| Ordering our software is 100% safe! When you place an order, your credit card number and personal information is protected by encrypting it. Encryption scrambles your credit card number and personal information. It stays scrambled while traveling over the Net and remains scrambled even while it is verified and processed. Your credit card number is not kept or recorded by Top Password Software, Inc. or any of our affiliates - it is simply passed through to the credit card company to finalize the purchase.   
---  
  
## Personal Information  
  
| We collect basic contact information when you fill in a order form. This information will be used for administrative and identification purposes only and will not be shared with our partners or third parties.   
---  
  
## Software  
  
| The software we create and that is distributed on our site does not collect any personal information or send any information to our server.   
---  
  
## Server Log Files  
  
| We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the web site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
